

LET'S CONNECT

+ 1 (408) 728 3006

sharontsang96@yahoo.com sharontsang96.wixsite.com/design Sharon's LinkedIn

SKILLS

Competitor Analysis
User Research & Surveys
User Personas
User Flows
User Stories
Usability Testing
Wireframing
Responsive Design
Prototyping
High-fidelity Mock-ups
Graphic Design
Concept art & Digital Illustration
Marketing Automation

TOOLS

+ DESIGN

Sketch Figma InVision Flinto Illustrator Photoshop InDesign Lightroom

+ MARKETING

Hootsuite Marketo WordPress

SHARON TSANG

UI/UX DESIGNER

UI/UX designer with a duality focus in graphic design and marketing. Experienced in visual graphic design, B2B marketing, social media marketing, lead generation research, logistics, product management, and illustration. Well-versed in communications and developing visual narration through design in branding and imagery.

EDUCATION

+ Certified in UI/UX Design | Front-end Development MAY 2021 Career Foundry

+ BS in Marketing | Minor in Graphic Design DEC 2018
San Jose State University

EXPERIENCE

+ Design & Illustration Freelance

MAR 2017 - CURRENT

Independently manage an e-commerce storefront, maintain social media presence, and lead product design and management, while designing visuals for product promotions.

+ Marketing Intern | Zingbox | Mountain View, CA

JUN 2019 - OCT 2019

Maintained the company's website and its social media accounts by curating blog articles, press releases, events. Constructed the marketing team's competitor analyses and presentations.

+ Marketing Office Assistant | Walden Technology Group | Milpitas, CA

APR 2017 - JAN 2019

Collaborated in designing the marketing collateral and additional marketing campaigns as the co-creative director.

+ SJSU H&A Marketing | Digital Marketing Intern | San Jose, CA

FEB 2018 - JUL 2018

Managed social media accounts and promotions through Hootsuite, and conducted marketing research to build contact database.

PROJECTS

+ SPACE

A uniquly branded mobile dating app that encourages users to meet genuine connections through fun, interactive, and engaging features.

+ YELP Mobile Redesign

A collaborative project analyzing Yelp's core issues and finding the right solutions in order to improve the user experience of the app.

+ Papriapples

An app that locates farmer's markets in local communities, organizes shopping lists, view updates, and bookmarks events.